Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Athletics, Communications, Records SC0367
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Records, 1987-1998; Accession ARCH-1999-273
  - Women's Basketball Box Scores, 1989-1989 (cont'd) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Women's Basketball Box Scores, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Women's Basketball Box Scores, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Women's Basketball Box Scores, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Women's Basketball Post-Season Books 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Women's Basketball Post-Season Books 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Women's Basketball Post-Season Books 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Women's Basketball Post-Season Books 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Women's Basketball Post-Season Books 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Binder--Women's Basketball, 1996-1997 (Box 12)
  - Binder--Men's Basketball, 1996-1997 (Box 12)
  - Binder--Basketball 1997 (Box 12)
  - Binder--All Sports: Crew to Soccer, 1996-1997 (Box 13)
  - Binder--All Sports: Softball to Wrestling, 1996-1997 (Box 13)
  - Binder--Releases, 1996-1997 (Box 13)
  - 1990 NCAA Women's Basketball Championships, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Women's Basketball -- "The Tara Van Derveer Show" 12/13/1993 and 12/27/1993, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - NCAA Selection Show on ESPN 3/13/1994, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Women's Basketball Player Katie Starbird 1994-1995, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Women's Basketball Player Anita Kaplan 1994-1995, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - NCAA Women's Basketball-Massachusetts vs. Stanford 12/6/1996, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Women's Basketball-Oregon vs. Stanford 1/16/1997, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Women's Basketball-USC vs. Stanford 2/6/1997, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Women's Basketball Preview 1997-1998, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - 1998 NCAA Women's Final Four Tribute-Kansas City Organizing Committee, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - NCAA 1998 Women's Final Four, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Women's NCAA Final Four Championship 3/23-29/1999, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Women's NCAA Final Four (on FOX Network), 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Compaq/NCAA Women's Final Four 2/23/1999, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Compaq/NCAA Women's Final Four 2/25/1999, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - ESPN High Heel Sneakers (Women's Basketball) 2/27/1997, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - ESPN High Heel Sneakers (Women's Basketball) 2/27/1999, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Basketball Highlights 1/24/1998, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Basketball Highlights 1/24/1998, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Women's Volleyball 12/17-19/1992, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Laxmi Popuri on ABC's Nightline 9/2/1994 & Bill Walsh's intro to Monday Nite Football 9/5/1994, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Football--1991 Aloha Bowl-Stanford vs. Georgia Tech, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Football--Stanford vs. Virginia 4/4/1992, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Football--Stanford vs. Western Kentucky 4/5/1992, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - A Team to Remember Highlights, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Stanford vs. North Dakota 36-31, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Road Trip, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Highlights from Washington 3/12/1994, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Sparkids, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Sports Journal, Program #30, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - 1996-1997 Honda Awards Program 1/12/1998, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Read to Succeed KICU-TV 11/26/1995, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Blank VHS Video? (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Heads 1997-1998 Women's, 1 videotape(s) (betacam) (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Blank BETA Tape? (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - NCAA Women's Final Four/Hoop City, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Blank Cassette Tape?, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Additional Records, 1987-1999; Accession ARCH-2003-203
  - Baseball, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Baseball, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Baseball northeast regional, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - College World Series, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Baseball, releases and clippings, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Baseball annual file, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Baseball post-season, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Baseball box scores, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Baseball final wrap-up, season stats, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Baseball individual honors, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Baseball Midwest I Regional, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - College World Series, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Basketball, men's, 1994-95 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Basketball, men's, final report, 1995-96 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cross country, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Fencing, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Field Hockey, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Field Hockey NCAA's, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Golf, men's, 1994-95 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Golf, men's, 1995-96 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Golf, women's, 1989-90 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Golf, women's, 1990-91 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Golf, women's, 1991-92 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Golf, women's, 1992-93 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Golf, women's, NCAA's, 1992-93 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Golf, women's, 1993-94 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Golf, women's, 1994-95 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Gymnastics, men's 1992-93 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Gymnastics, men's, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Gymnastics, men's 1993-94 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Gymnastics, men's, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Gymnastics, men's, season's results, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Gymnastics, men's 1995-96 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Gymnastics, women's, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Gymnastics, women's, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Gymnastics, women's, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Soccer, men's, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Soccer, men's, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Soccer, women's, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Softball, year-end, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Softball 1995-96 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Softball 1999 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Women's swimming and diving, 1992-93 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Women's swimming and diving, 1993-94 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Women's swimming and diving, 1994-95 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Women's swimming and diving, NCAA's, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Synchronized Swimming 1993-94 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Synchronized Swimming 1994-95 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Synchronized Swimming 1995-96 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Tennis, men's 1987-88 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Tennis, men's 1988-89 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Tennis, men's 1989-90 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Tennis, men's 1990-91 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Tennis, men's 1991-92 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Tennis, men's, NCAA's 1992-93 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Tennis, men's 1993-94 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Tennis, men's 1994-95 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Tennis, women's 1987-88 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Tennis, women's 1989-90 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Tennis, women's 1990-91 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Tennis, women's 1991-92 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Tennis, women's 1992-93 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Tennis, women's 1993-94 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Tennis, women's 1994-95 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Track and field, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Track and field, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Track and field, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Track and field, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Track and field, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Track and field, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Track and field, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Volleyball, men's 1987 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Volleyball, men's, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Volleyball, men's, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Volleyball, men's, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Volleyball, men's, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Volleyball, men's, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Volleyball, men's, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Volleyball, men's, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Volleyball, men's, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Volleyball, women's, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Volleyball, women's, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Volleyball, women's, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Volleyball, women's, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Volleyball, women's, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Volleyball, women's, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Volleyball, women's, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Volleyball, women's, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Volleyball, women's, NCAA's, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Water polo, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Water polo, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Water polo, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Water polo, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Water polo, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Water polo, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Water polo, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Water polo, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Water polo, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Water polo, NCAA championship, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Wrestling 1987-88 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Wrestling 1988-89 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Wrestling 1989-90 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Wrestling 1990-91 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Wrestling 1991-92 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Wrestling 1992-93 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Wrestling 1993-94 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Wrestling 1994-95 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Wrestling 1995-96 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Photographs, 1935-1950; Accession ARCH-2006-227
  - Sam Klopstock (1 photo), circa 1935 (Box 1)
  - Photo strips of pole vaults, high jumps, etc. (possibly printed versions of film strips in Film 134), 1950s (Box 1)
- Additional Records, 1931-1972; Accession ARCH-2006-331
  - Golf record book, 1931-46 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Golf record book, 1949-54 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Golf record book, 1955-72 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Clippings from golf record books (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous records from volumes, 1939, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Additional Records, 2005-2008; Accession ARCH-2008-200
  - Annual Awards Luncheon, 2005, 2007, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Hall of Fame Inductees (program), 2007 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - New Stanford Stadium Postseason Report, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Women's Golf Records, 1939-1951; Accession ARCH-2006-246
  - Golf, women's (Boxed with accession 2006-311), 1939-1951 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Pacific Coast Intercollegiate Athletic Conference Survey Report, 1939; Accession ARCH-2009-217
  - Pacific Coast Intercollegiate Athletic Conference Survey Report [Stanford University portion] by Edwin N. Atherton & Associates, (c. 1), 1939 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Pacific Coast Intercollegiate Athletic Conference Survey Report [Stanford University portion] by Edwin N. Atherton & Associates, (c. 2), 1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)